ILR School Dean's Office Files /3085
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Audio-Visual Materials Lab, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Establishment of Industrial Education Program, 1946-1950 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- ST-1-4 Scholarships (1946-50), 1946-1950 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Joint Legislative Committee on Housing + Multiple, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Board of Trustees, 1946-1948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- E-1 Extension, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Extension 1948(2) (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Extension 1948 (3) (Box 20, Folder 5)
- FS-1 Fiscal, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- R-1 Research 1947-48, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Research Letter + Replies on those attending research Conf. - Nov. - Dec. 1948 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- ST-1-2 Undergraduate Curric. 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- ST-1-8 Extra - Mural Course, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Graduate Curriculum, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- ST-2-1 General, 1947-1948 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 Applicants, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 A-B, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 A-B, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 D, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 E, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- G-1-2 F, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 G, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 H, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 I-J, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 K, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 L, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 M, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 N, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 O and P, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 Q-R, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- G-1-2 S, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 T-U, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- G-1-2 W-X, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- G-1-2 Y-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- G-1-2 A, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- G-1-2 B, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- G-1-2 C, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- G-1-2 D, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- G-1-2 E, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- G-1-2 F, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- G-1-2 G, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- G-1-2 H, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- G-1-2 I-J, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- G-1-2 A, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 B, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 C, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 D, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- G-1-2 D, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- G-1-2 E, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- G-1-2 F, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 G, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- G-1-2 H, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- G-1-2 I, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- G-1-2 J, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- G-1-2 K, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- G-1-2 L, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- G-1-2 M, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- G-1-2 N, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- G-1-2 O, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- G-1-2 P, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- G-1-2 R, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- G-1-2 S, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- G-1-2 T, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- G-1-2 U-V, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- G-1-2 W, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- G-1-2 X-Y-Z, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- H-K, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- E-1 Extension (general), 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Summer Sessions, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Extension, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- M-1, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- M-1, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- M-(con't), 1948 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- G-1-2 S, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- G-1-2 O, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- G-1-2 M, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- N- Cont., 1948-1949 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- R- Cont., 1949 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- S- Con't., 1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- G-1-2 Z, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- P-6 Staff Applicants - A, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Staff Applicants BA-Bl, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Staff Applicants Bo-By, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Staff Applicant Ca-Ch, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Staff Applicants Cl-Cu, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Staff Applicants D, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Staff Applicants E, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Staff Applicants F, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Staff Applicants Ga-Ge, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Staff Applicants Gl-Gu, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Staff Applicants Ha., 1946 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Staff Applicants He - Hu, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Staff Applicants I, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Staff Applicants J, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Staff Applicants K, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Staff Applicants L, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Staff Applicants Mc-Me, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Staff Applicants Mi-My, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Staff Applicants N-O, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Staff Applicants Pa-Peck, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Staff Applicants Per-Po, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Staff Applicants Re-Rob, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Staff Applicants Rog-Ry, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Staff Applicants Sa-Sch, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Staff Applicants Sh-Sic., 1946 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Staff Applicants T, 1945 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Staff Applicants V-Z, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Administrative Conference, 1952-1953 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Administrative Conference, 1953-1954 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Administrative Conference, 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Advisory Council - 1952 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Board of Trustees -1948 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees - 1949 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Board of Trustees - 1950 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees - 1951 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees - 1952 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees - 1953 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Refill, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Roll Book, 1949-1950 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Family Muting - 1952 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- 1949 - Former Graduate Assistants (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Graduate Assistants - Fall 1951 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Graduate Assistantships, 1949-1950 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Graduate Assistantship, 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Graduate Assistantships - Spring 1952 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Grad. Assistants and Grad. Students, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Research Associates + Instructors, 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Professional Employees - Possibilities, 1949 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- A to Z - 1949-'51, 1949-1951 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Applicants - Openings - Resignations, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Job Classification - Administration Library Maintenance, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Human Relations within American Hospitals, 1950-1952 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Gordon, Paul Regional Council Hospital Research, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Estey, Marten Labor Relations in Retail Grocery Stores, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Crucible Steel, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Buffalo Construction Industry Study, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Brophy, John M. Executive Training for Foreign Service, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Bradburd Term Paper, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Billmyer, David, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Bell Aircraft, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Beal, Edwin F., 1952 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Beach Bibliography, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- L. Adams: Docks Labor Project Plan, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Materials Lab -- Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Audio - Visual Data + Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- L-3 Audio Visual Aids, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- PU-8 Distribution Center, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- G-5 Educational Directory, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Faculty Meetings - 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- A-2 Faculty Meetings - 1953 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Fall Faculty Meeting - 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Annual Faculty Meeting - September 1953 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- National Social Welfare Association Youth Division Assembly, August 5-17, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Advisory Council 1954 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- PU-1 Publications General Correspondence, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- PU-8-1 Weekly Distribution Reports, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Monthly Distribution Reports, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- PU-8-4 Bulletin Inventory, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- PU-8-5 Bulletin Distribution, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- PU-2-1 ILR Review Correspondence, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- PU-2-2 ILR Review Copyright, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- PU-2-3 ILR Review Postage, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- PU-2-4 ILR Review Printing, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- PU-2-5 ILR Review Subscription Reports, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- PU-2-6 ILR Review Financial Reports, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- PU-2-7 ILR Review Subscription Lists, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- PU-2-8 ILR Review Promotion, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- PU-3 Bulletins, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- PU-4-1 Cornell Studies Copyright, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- PU-4 Cornell Studies in ILR, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- PU-5 Abstracts and Annotations, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- PU-6 School Promotion Material, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- PU-7 School Catalogue, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Job Classification - Correspondence Blank Statements, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- M-2 1949-50 Conference, Meetings, Exhibits, 1949-1950 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Conference Financial Statements - 1953 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- 1952 Conferences (Box 27, Folder 23)
- 1951 Conferences (Budget Info.) (Box 27, Folder 24)
- M-3-2d Conf. Institutes, etc. 9-52 to 8-53, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- M-3-3 ILR Faculty Reply to Conference Memo., 1953 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Summer Session -1953- Seminar and Workshops (Box 27, Folder 27)
- M-3-2d Proceedings, Teamwork in Industry, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- M-3-2d Proceedings, Training Directors, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Budget and Finance, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Conferences and Institutes S.S., 1949 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Course Offerings S.S. '48 to, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Enrollment S.S. '50 to, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Post Sessions S.S., 1952 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Seminar and Workshops - General S.S., 1954 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Seminars---Wk.. Evaluation Questionnaires, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Staff SS, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Student Surveys S.S., 1950 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous S.S. '48 to, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Library Facilities - 1947 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Hist. of the School, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Hist. of the School, 1944-1946 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Hist. of the School, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- H-2-1 -1946- (Box 28, Folder 5)
- E-1 Extension - General, 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- E-2 Extension Program + Policy, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- F-1 Fiscal - General, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- E-1 Extension - N.Y.C, Meeting, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- NYSSILR Workers Education Conference, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- NYSSILR Workers Education Conference, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- A-3 Advisory Council Meeting, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- A-3 Advisory Council Meeting 6-4-46, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Temporary Building ILR, 1946 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Dean's Notes, Reports, etc., 1947 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Annual Report. Extension Division, 1946-1947 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- E-1 Extension Conference, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Preliminary Budget Request 76-77, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Fiscal Final Budget Request, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Preliminary Budget Request 1975/76, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Final Budget Request 1975/76, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- FY 1978/79 Final Budget Request, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Final Budget Request, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Division Directors Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Academic Plan, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Enrollment Projections, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Inputs + Outputs - 1961-1965 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Annual Report 1965-66, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- PR-60, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- PR-62, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- PR-2, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 14)